<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tourist Picture</string>
    <string name="picture1">Mount Kilimanjaro located in Tanzania. Mount Kilimanjaro is the highest free standing mountain in the world and it is also the highest mountain of the African continent</string>
    <string name="picture2">This alley of baobab trees is named Allée de Baobab in French. This scenic landscape is located in western Madagascar.About 25 huge baobabs trees line a stretch of road about 30 km/ 18 miles.</string>
    <string name="picture3">The Great Pyramid of Gizais the oldest and largest of the three pyramids in a pyramid complex. The pyramids of Giza are located near Cairo in Egypt.</string>
    <string name="picture4">One of the most iconic and most photographed mountain silhouettes (or profile) is that of Table Mountain in Cape Town/South Africa. </string>
    <string name="picture5">Timbuktu is a city in Mali that is situated on the ancient trade route of the Mali Empire. Timbuktu is located on the southern edge of the Sahara</string>
    <string name="picture6">The Vallée de Mai on the Seychelles island of Praslin is another UNESCO world heritage site. This tropical rainforest in the islands interior is known for its palm trees with the huge coco-de-mer seeds.</string>
    <string name="picture7">The Victoria Falls are the worlds largest waterfalls during the wet season and one of the Seven Natural Wonders of the World. The waterfalls are referred to as Mosi-oa-Tunya (The smoke that thunders) by the Zambians</string>
    <string name="picture8">The Basilica of Our Lady of Peace is located in Yamoussoukro in Côte dIvoire, which was formerly called Ivory Coast.</string>
    <string name="picture9">The Great Mosque of Algiers, also called Djamaa El Djazair, is Africas largest mosque. The mosque in Algeria capital city Algiers was completed in 2019 after seven years of construction. </string>
    <string name="picture10">The dunes of the Namib-Naukluft Nationalpark in Namibia are the highest dunes in the world. They are up to 300 m/ 1000 ft high. </string>
</resources>